<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Manuel Rguez-Sánchez</title>
    <link>http://manuelrdsg.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Manuel Rguez-Sánchez</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-uk</language>
    <lastBuildDate>Fri, 12 Oct 2018 00:00:00 +0000</lastBuildDate>
    
	<atom:link href="http://manuelrdsg.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>Improving the look of your MacOS Terminal</title>
      <link>http://manuelrdsg.github.io/2018/10/improving-the-look-of-your-macos-terminal/</link>
      <pubDate>Fri, 12 Oct 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://manuelrdsg.github.io/2018/10/improving-the-look-of-your-macos-terminal/</guid>
      <description>Since I upgraded my Mac to the latest Mojave build, due to it&amp;rsquo;s Dark Mode I was wanting to change the look of my MacOS Terminal.
So, after searching and going through a few tutorials I have completely changed the look of my terminal, here you will find a tutorial about which steps have I made to change my terminal.
Step 1: Get rid off the default terminal If we want to choose a different terminal emulator, in MacOS there are two main options:</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>HeroDemo a GLSL Shaders project</title>
      <link>http://manuelrdsg.github.io/2018/04/herodemo-a-glsl-shaders-project/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 23 Apr 2018 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://manuelrdsg.github.io/2018/04/herodemo-a-glsl-shaders-project/</guid>
      <description>Through the last year I have been learning OpenGL and Shader programming with GLSL. I started learning the basics of OpenGL, how to render objects, how to place them in the scene; and also the basics of shader programming, how the pipeline works and how to render basic effects like directional or ambient lightning.
After months learning OpenGL and GLSL I have developed this example project called Hero Demo it is a night scene, with particles effect, SkyBoxing, per-fragment point lightning, water rendering</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>De la ventana a la manzana</title>
      <link>http://manuelrdsg.github.io/2017/12/de-la-ventana-a-la-manzana/</link>
      <pubDate>Tue, 05 Dec 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://manuelrdsg.github.io/2017/12/de-la-ventana-a-la-manzana/</guid>
      <description>Veréis, en torno a Octubre-Septiembre del año pasado me invitaron a la pasada edición de Lambda World, un gran congreso centrado en el mundo de la programación funcional del que puede que hablemos en alguna que otra entrada.
Esta, era la primera vez que pisaba un congreso de la profesión y al margen de lo interesante de las ponencias y de las personas que conoces en este tipo de eventos hubo algo que me llamó bastante la atención, la gran mayoría (así a ojímetro) de los asistentes al congreso utilizaban OSX como plataforma de desarrollo.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>¡Conducen por la izquierda!</title>
      <link>http://manuelrdsg.github.io/2017/03/conducen-por-la-izquierda/</link>
      <pubDate>Sat, 25 Mar 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://manuelrdsg.github.io/2017/03/conducen-por-la-izquierda/</guid>
      <description>¡Hola a todos!
Hace no mucho me han confirmado que el año que viene (si todo va bien) estaré en Londres, cursando mi último año de carrera. Se me ha ocurrido que puede ser interesante relataros la aventura a lo largo de una serie de posts y de este modo, poder hacer retrospectiva cuando mi tiempo en Londres haya llegado a su fin.
“¿Estarás contento, no? “ Tras comunicar la noticia alguien me hizo la misma pregunta que reza en el título de la sección y me dejó bastante pensativo.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Yo he venido aquí a hablar de mi libro</title>
      <link>http://manuelrdsg.github.io/2015/05/yo-he-venido-aqu%C3%AD-a-hablar-de-mi-libro/</link>
      <pubDate>Wed, 13 May 2015 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://manuelrdsg.github.io/2015/05/yo-he-venido-aqu%C3%AD-a-hablar-de-mi-libro/</guid>
      <description>¡Hola a todos! Sed bienvenidos a este blog. Llevaba un tiempo con el interés de hacerme un blog personal donde, como reza en el título venir a hablar de mi libro, es decir, de cosas en general sin preocuparme demasiado. Y ya en el proceso aprender algo más de desarrollo web, vamos, un win/win que se dice.
¿Que me voy a encontrar? Pues un poco de todo, desde posts hablando de ocio en general (libros, pelis, juegos, música que me mole) a posts acerca de programación o desarrollo de videojuegos en el cual me encuentro inciandome en estos momentos.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>http://manuelrdsg.github.io/page/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://manuelrdsg.github.io/page/about/</guid>
      <description>Hi! I am Manuel, Full Stack developer at Intelygenz Software.
 You can take a look at my CV  Currently I&amp;rsquo;m working as a Full Stack developer at Intelygenz Software in Madrid, Spain. I&amp;rsquo;m focused in cross-platform techonologies as React Native and Ionic.
Past Work Cross-Platform frameworks: A comparative study Along with Intelygenz and the University of Cádiz, I developed an study about the performance of the most used Cross-Platform technologies in the software developement industry (React Native, Ionic, Weex and Flutter).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Personal Projects</title>
      <link>http://manuelrdsg.github.io/page/projects/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://manuelrdsg.github.io/page/projects/</guid>
      <description>Cross-Platform frameworks: A comparative study Developed as a collaboration project between Intelygenz Software and the University of Cádiz.
The study aimed to dispel doubts when choosing a cross-platform development. For this, the most used cross-platform frameworks in the software development industry (React Native, Ionic, Flutter and Weex) have been compared in terms of execution times and code quality, offering an objective comparison between them. This comparison has been made through the development of four benchmark applications, one in each of the frameworks and the measurement of metrics in them for the subsequent contrast of the data obtained.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>