<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Pages on Manuel Rguez-S치nchez</title>
    <link>http://manuelrdsg.github.io/page/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Pages on Manuel Rguez-S치nchez</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-uk</language>
    
	<atom:link href="http://manuelrdsg.github.io/page/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>About</title>
      <link>http://manuelrdsg.github.io/page/about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://manuelrdsg.github.io/page/about/</guid>
      <description>Hi! I am Manuel, Full Stack developer at Intelygenz Software.
 You can take a look at my CV  Currently I&amp;rsquo;m working as a Full Stack developer at Intelygenz Software in Madrid, Spain. I&amp;rsquo;m focused in cross-platform techonologies as React Native and Ionic.
Past Work Cross-Platform frameworks: A comparative study Along with Intelygenz and the University of C치diz, I developed an study about the performance of the most used Cross-Platform technologies in the software developement industry (React Native, Ionic, Weex and Flutter).</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Personal Projects</title>
      <link>http://manuelrdsg.github.io/page/projects/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>http://manuelrdsg.github.io/page/projects/</guid>
      <description>Cross-Platform frameworks: A comparative study Developed as a collaboration project between Intelygenz Software and the University of C치diz.
The study aimed to dispel doubts when choosing a cross-platform development. For this, the most used cross-platform frameworks in the software development industry (React Native, Ionic, Flutter and Weex) have been compared in terms of execution times and code quality, offering an objective comparison between them. This comparison has been made through the development of four benchmark applications, one in each of the frameworks and the measurement of metrics in them for the subsequent contrast of the data obtained.</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>